II MASHIR A.

MUHAMMAD NASHIR ALLATIF College Student

Contact

Muhammadnashir9@gmail.com



085867637368



Tegallayang, Caturharjo, Pandak, Bantul, Yogyakarta

Tools and Skills

Codeigniter

Laravel

CSS

JavaScript

Python

Reac Js

Other Skill

Videography

Graphic design

Personal

Leadership

Teamwork

On Time

Commitment

esian

ABOUT ME

Hi I'm Muhammad Nashir Allatif

I like to try new things in the world of technology, especially in website development, Not only that I sometimes play in graphic design.

The last 3 years I tried to get out of my comfort zone, participate in various organizations and play an active role in it

Education

2017 - : Univ. Ahmad Dahlan (Informatics Enginering)

2014-2017 : SMA N 1 Sanden

2011-2014 : SMP N 1 Srandakan

2006-2011 : SD Muh Tegallayang 1

2005-2006 : SD N 1 Guwosari

Experience

1. Organization Experience

2018 : Staff Public Relation (HMTIF)

2019 : Coordinator Public Relation (HMTIF)

♦ 2019 : Staff Research and Development PERMIKOMNAS WIL.8

♦ 2019-2021 : Chairman OPETRA (Youth Organizations)

2. Work Experience

2019 - 2020 : Lab Assintant

(web programming, Discrete mathematics, Database, objeck oriented programming, statistical informatics, computer graphics, algorithmic strategy)

2019 : Practical work in SD Muh Tegallayang 1